Welcome back to this training. In this tutorial, we'll be discussing about Windows Server in depth.
We'll also be discussing about Microsoft. Please describe Azure Active Directory and Microsoft Intune.
This is going to be a practical based training and little theory.
So what are we going to be discussing in this tutorial?
First of all, we're going to be configuring our lab.
I'm going to show you how to configure your lab so that you'll be able to follow up with this tutorial.
And there will not move to install our Windows Server and Configure our servers.
Next, I'll be showing you how to install our Windows client and also configure our client machines.
Then we'll also be understanding Active Directory infrastructure.
Next, we're going to look at Active Directory domain services, organizational unit, users and groups.
Then we'll now move to an attend group, policies.
And then we'll also be discussing about how to deploy Azure Active Directory Connect.
Then we'll now go in depth to understand DNS servers.
I will also be showing you how to install, configure and manage DHCP server.
We'll also be monitoring storage and file services in our Windows domain environment.
If you have a domain environment, definitely you want to actually configure a high availability.
I'm going to show you how to configure that.
We'll also be discussing about identity and access solution.
Next, we'll now go ahead to discuss about continuity and disaster recovery in our domain environment.
Now we'll now move to discuss about Microsoft Intune, how to implement mobile device management with Microsoft Intune.
I'll be showing you how to manage Windows software update services.
We're going to be installing implementing a managing Windows software update service.
Then we're going to configure in a Windows server platform file system, and also we'll be discussing about bits, locker and encryption.
Then lastly, we're going to be doing a Windows server performance on maintenance.
So this is going to be a practical base training.
Definitely you want to have a desktop or a laptop at your disposal to be able to follow up on this training from the beginning.
the beginning to the end.